import {IQuestion} from "@/store/questions/questions.types";

export const mediumCountriesData: IQuestion[] = [
    {
        question: 'What country is known as the Land of the Rising Sun?',
        correct_answer: 'Japan'
    },
    {
        question: 'What country is known as the Land of the Midnight Sun?',
        correct_answer: 'Norway'
    },
    {
        question: 'What country is known as the Land of the Long White Cloud?',
        correct_answer: 'New Zealand'
    },
    {
        question: 'What country is known as the Land of the Thunder Dragon?',
        correct_answer: 'Bhutan'
    },
    {
        question: 'What country is known as the Land of the Free?',
        correct_answer: 'United States'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Eiffel Tower?',
        correct_answer: 'France'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Big Ben?',
        correct_answer: 'United Kingdom'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Kremlin?',
        correct_answer: 'Russia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Colosseum?',
        correct_answer: 'Italy'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Taj Mahal?',
        correct_answer: 'India'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Christ the Redeemer?',
        correct_answer: 'Brazil'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Great Wall of China?',
        correct_answer: 'China'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Sydney Opera House?',
        correct_answer: 'Australia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Statue of Liberty?',
        correct_answer: 'United States'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Machu Picchu?',
        correct_answer: 'Peru'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Stonehenge?',
        correct_answer: 'United Kingdom'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Acropolis?',
        correct_answer: 'Greece'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Sagrada Familia?',
        correct_answer: 'Spain'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find St. Basil Cathedral?',
        correct_answer: 'Russia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Neuschwanstein Castle?',
        correct_answer: 'Germany'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Petra?',
        correct_answer: 'Jordan'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Angkor Wat?',
        correct_answer: 'Cambodia'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Chichen Itza?',
        correct_answer: 'Mexico'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Alhambra?',
        correct_answer: 'Spain'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Potala Palace?',
        correct_answer: 'Tibet'
    },
    {
        question: 'Where you can find Hagia Sophia?',
        correct_answer: 'Turkey'
    },
    ];